Guide to the School of Hotel Administration Executive Education records, 1981-1985.
School of Hotel Administration Executive Education records, 1981-1985
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
School of Hotel Administration Executive Education records, 1981-1985.
28-6-2415
Cornell University. School of Hotel Administration.Executive Education.
2 cubic ft.
Correspondence and other documents.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Records of seminars prior to 1986 and general correspondence.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records of seminars prior to 1986 and general correspondence.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University. School of Hotel Administration.Executive Education.
Subjects:
Hotel management--Study and teaching.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission ofoffice of origin.
CONTAINER LIST
- Japan Travel Bureau, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Japan Travel Bureau, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Syracuse China, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Syracuse China, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Pinnacle Club, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
- Super 8 Motels, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Society for Foodservice Management (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Quality Inns (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Cotelco, Mar., May 1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Cotelco, Aug. 1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Cotelco, Nov. 1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Owens Corning, June 1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- NICCO Hotels, Oct. 1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Cotelco, Nov. 1982 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Cotelco, Aug. 1982 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Cotelco, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Cotelco, Dec. 1982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Cyprus Hotels, Jan. 1985 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- EGOTH, Jan. 1984 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Helsinki Hotel School, June 1983 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- German Program, Sept. 1983 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Maui Economic Board, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- ISS Center for Mgt Devel., Dec. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- ISS Center for Mgt Devel., 1983 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- ISS Center for Mgt Devel., Sept. 1983 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- ISS Center for Mgt Devel., Jan. 1984 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- ISS Center for Mgt Devel., 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Cotelco, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Cotelco, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Cotelco, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- CMAA Metropolitan, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Hilton Int'l-CDI, NY, Aug. 1985 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- BOCES, Dec. 1984 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- AMX-Europe Ltd., Jan. 1985 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Colorado-Wyoming Rest. Assoc., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Coldwater Seafood Corp., Oct. 1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- American Express Europe Ltd., 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- American Express Europe Ltd., Nov. 1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Airlanka Catering Services, Ltd. (Box 2, Folder 4)
- American Automobile Assoc., Apr. 1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- JTB, May 1982 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- JTB, May 1983 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Japan Foodservice, Aug. 1982 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Japan Foodservice, Aug. 1984 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Japan Foodservice, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Jamaica Tourist Board, July 1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- India Tourism-ITDC, July 1984 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- HSMA, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Hilton Int'l - Sidney, Aug. 1985 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Hilton Int'l - Sidney, Jan. 1985 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Helsinki Hotel School (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Financial Management in the 80s, June 1983 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Nat'l Ass. Meat Purveyors-NAMP, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Nat'l Ass. Meat Purveyors-NAMP, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- NAFEM, Mar. 1982 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- NAFEM, Mar. 1985 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- NAFEM, Jan. 1984 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Solstrand Fjord, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Solstrand Fjord, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Solstrand Fjord, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Syracuse China, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 26)